neowin.net 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Neowin

## Privacy Policy

  1. #### Visitor Notice

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before participating on the message boards, entering a contest, or ordering e-mail newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

    * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
    * To help you quickly find services or information on neowin.net.
    * To help us create content most relevant to you.
    * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from neowin.net.
  2. #### Visitor Consent

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on neowin.net, but you will not be able to access areas that require registration. neowin.net may offer newsletters, which are sent only to opt-in lists. They also include a very easy and simple way to be removed once you have joined.

  3. #### Security

neowin.net strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

  4. #### Distribution of personal information

neowin.net does not distribute personal information to any third parties. Should this change, neowin.net will not distribute any information without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on neowin.net, that some of your personal information is available on publically accessible web page(s). One example would be using the neowin.net forums. Consent to expose some of your personal information in these cases is implied by the use of these features.

  5. #### Hosted Sites

neowin.net gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. In order to comply with the COPPA ruling, if you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of Neowin.net or posting information on Neowin.net message boards without direct parental consent.

  6. #### Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. If so, a list of these ad serving companies will be [available here](http://www.neowin.net/advertising/). These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer web site at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

  7. #### Spam Protection

Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)  
Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.  
The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/). 

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/).

  8. #### Measuring our visitors

We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site. The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better. You can learn more about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) or [opt out if you wish](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

  9. #### Enforcement

If for some reason you believe neowin.net have not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at [privacy@neowin.net](mailto:privacy@neowin.net), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

  10. #### Changes to this document

Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. neowin.net may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.

**Notice to Parents or Guardians:** We want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

View our [DMCA Policy](http://www.neowin.net/dmca).
